<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lucas Galdino</title>
    <link>https://www.lucasgaldino.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lucas Galdino</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:16:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.lucasgaldino.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.lucasgaldino.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lucasgaldino.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Brazilian-Canadian programmer and student of biology living in Sherbrooke, Quebec. I am fascinated by how our mind works, and how it affects our experience of reality. In particular, I want to understand how it is shaped by the various rituals, habits, and practices that permeate our daily life.
In this website, as well as in my YouTube channel, I will be publishing various articles, essays, and videos on the subjects of neuroscience, health, technology, and phylosophy.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I am a Brazilian-Canadian programmer and student of biology living in Sherbrooke, Quebec.
I am fascinated by how our mind works, and how it affects our experience of reality.
In particular, I want to understand how it is shaped by the various
rituals, habits, and practices that permeate our daily life.</p>
<p>In this website, as well as in my <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@imlucasgaldino">YouTube channel,</a> I will be publishing
various articles, essays, and videos on the
subjects of neuroscience, health, technology, and phylosophy.
I will also, occasionally, share some free-form writing, such as poems
or thoughts.</p>
<p>My goal in this endeavour is to discover, research, and experiment
with different practices and their effect on our mental and physical health,
and to share this discovery with you. We&rsquo;ll discuss how to apply these tools
in daily life and the science behind them. Because I believe science should be
made available to all. Health should be made available to all.</p>
<p>I hope that you might find some value and enjoyment in my videos and writings.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
